不然她为什么放在保险箱里呢
Why else would she have kept it in her strongbox?
你不会信了那些鬼话吧
You're not telling me you believed all that guff, are you?
柯兹洛娃夫人在书里画了十二座伦敦的地标建筑
Madame Kozlova drew 12 London landmarks in that book.
所以呢
Yes?
如果它们不仅仅是地标呢 如果是...
Well, what if they're not just landmarks? What if they're...
-可能是线索呢  -线索
- I don't know, clues? - Clues?
-寻找财宝的线索  -你是说藏宝图吗
- To where she hid her fortune. - You mean a treasure map?
没错
Exactly!
所以小偷才从格鲁伯的店那把书偷走
And that's why the thief took it from Mr Gruber's.
明天一早
First thing tomorrow,
我们就去书里的那些地标建筑
we need to go to every landmark in that book.
说不定能找到什么线索
See if we can sniff out anything suspicious.
-你这是冒险故事看太多了吧 玛丽  -什么
- Too many adventure stories, Mary. - What?